No call over the various given meeting bombs.
The Council for Monday, March 4, 2020, will work.
Public input.
Let's go to the Purple Features.
We have none.
Three primalists.
Mr. Bruce.
Second.
He's been subvert.
Double time.
Williams.
Parker.
Five minutes in the February 20th.
At February 26th.
Twenty-four.
We're going to skip a V.
Mr. Bruce.
He's been subvert.
Double.
Williams.
Five presentations.
Nine areas.
No concerns.
This is what Mr. Chan knew.
It's great.
Some of the people came out to hear about presentation.
I have a really appreciate that.
So what I wanted to do tonight is update you on Jim Fram's plan.
That he's working on us.
Our economic development is approaching action.
That plan is completed.
I think that the rough draft of that plan.
Here's your work.
I have a meeting with Jim.
Today is your meeting.
Just kind of go over some questions that I have.
I have an audio information that's in this plan.
Mainly what I want to tell you is.
And this will all be rolled out by the end of March.
We'll have a public forum.
Here in this room.
Sometimes you're the end of March.
We'll roll this plan out after this mid-tweet and edited.
To the public.
But one of the things I was encouraging about this plan is.
In this plan.
Excuse me, my apologies.
There's a lot of things.
In this plan that we've already had conversations about.
There are things in this plan that we are actually all ready to begin to work on.
And what's important about that.
And why that's encouraging is that it means we're on the right track.
We're having the right conversations.
And so when you talk about economic development.
That's a great broad term.
And there's a lot of things that go in to economic development.
It's fresh bonds.
It's retail.
It's manufacturing.
It's other industry.
It's entrepreneurship.
But one of the things that stuck out to me.
It's not new information.
But it's just a great opportunity to reiterate it.
Why do we do what we do?
Why do we happen to these conversations?
And when we talk about economic development.
And we talk about all of those things.
And we talk about adding jobs to our diversity.
Of which it keeps the numbers in mind.
Of why we have to do this and why it's so important.
The average of UV and household income.
I don't know.
$46,000. That's household income. In the city of Miami alone, there are 23% of our
residents living in poverty. And when you talk about $46,000, median household income of
the Iowa County, consider that the average, the average, individual salary, for full
time of wage, salary, workers of the United States, is $59,000. The average median household
income in the country is $75,000. So when we talk about economic development, we talk about
all the things that we need in our community. We need to make sure that everything we do is
designed to raise the board. It's not just about community jobs, it's about community jobs,
I mean, if our residents out from underneath the poverty level, it's about raising that
$46,000 household income higher. It's about creating opportunities so that every free one, we
raise the board for all of our residents. Not just in Miami, not just in Iowa County, but in collaboration
with our Native American farmers and our other area of counties, we can have a tremendous impact
by working together. And this report talks about the importance of collaboration. It talks about a
regional approach. The city of Miami is still on the look for its own plan. Because you have
things that we can't decide for you. You have to make sure that you're a properly planning for
utility of brings. You're properly addressing that I saw a post today about a mystery being done.
That streets are being improved. That you have a plan to make sure that we have the best training
and best equipped, far and police protection we can possibly have in Miami. On the time of
you take care of all of that, there's not a whole lot of money left over in the budget, right? So,
prior to our size of those dollars, it's an issue where addressing those economic developments,
it's important. And that's why partners play such an important role in that. Mays, Miami,
Vietnam, and Development Service, the city of Miami, all of the municipalities within this
town are tribal partners, all have to work together and for going to be successful. This plan is only
this good as our ability to work together. It's genius.
And so I'm excited about what we're seeing in this report.
Look, as it solve all of our major issues,
no-go-to-mechanical recommendations on things
that you're doing that you need to keep doing,
and it talks about some things that you can add
in a normal way, to address those key issues,
like flooding, to address the issues like housing,
to address the issues like economic development,
creating jobs, and all of those,
so that everyone can find the job,
everyone can be successful,
and everyone can finally,
and I am an adult, and I get a change in the American Treaty.
That's what we're working toward.
That's the purpose of this plan.
And I hope that you get job opportunities
to review it here in a few weeks,
that you'll see that there's a ton of opportunity here,
if we're willing to work together,
so maybe have a happy answer to any other questions
along those lines.
So, Mayor, we're going to be in Council.
So, Jim Bray, who makes his contract
with the Health Development, this ex-cute will economic development plan.
This document, he said, you should see it in the finished form
in a few weeks.
Correct.
Around that time, I'm asked Jim Bray,
in terms of speaking to the Council,
to answer any questions anybody would have,
not being the plan that he's provided
and also talked to us about.
The possibility of working with Jim to update our confidence
to plan for your decision and creating an opportunity to do
to do that economic development plan for May,
and to do it with the opportunity to do it.
And they'll see our confidence in the plan.
And follow those points.
They're asked in this plan.
That don't directly want to happen with some of the names
of our generator.
Thank you.
Six.
Or at least part of the three of them,
can you question some of those two meetings?
One, two, one and two.
PC, one and phi.
And one of those, two, one, four.
you think this isn't a long running tough.
That's a question, what's broad enough?
And the question is, do you want to respond recently?
So, what would a conditional ask you to do?
0.6, 1% grand light came in the middle of the period of time, and it was to say it's
of 2,027,36 under the vast closest bit, which is first action by it.
And we want to recommend it.
Thank you very much.
So, the basic movement was a growth club for the armory location teams that had been
nasi behind 14 first time in New York West, and some were eaten by a graduation program.
So, many of the members of the Council have just declared that there's no expectation that the Council
have been making a decision on this contract tonight.
So, we're going to have to work very, very short time.
But the contract tonight is presented really so that it could be made one available on the community.
And then, so that you have plenty of opportunity to review, discuss, and ask questions.
A little background work at 4K, and maybe more details, of course.
A city of Wyoming has a long term, makes agreement with one of the girls club for the armory location team at the very park.
In addition to that, the city is seeking to re-negotiate that contract.
So, in terms of conditions, we can be upgraded.
And so, in that process, we also had identified that there was also opportunity that we were looking to explore
with the girls of the often expanded summer program, a place of the city that's our people.
Additionally, as we regret in the agenda item, the club is also recently acquired building a downtown environment
with the potential establishment of teens in it, with the use of state funds to build a gym on city property,
directly adjacent to that facility.
So, the staff was charged with going and looking at all of these items to tell me, and figure out, you know,
whether there be a way to address these challenges, and for closely speaking, we could solve the overall conditions in your seat of document.
So, the agreement seeks to find unified solutions a bit of it, both parties.
So, again, it's a pretty complex document, because it's taking on several elements into one down.
So, again, we're not able to rush to do everything.
We want to give you all to look at it, and answer any questions in my ask.
Kevin, do you want to kind of give us a few tales about some things you want to give you a go-shake?
You know, a lot of those said the racial agreement was back in 2012.
Do that as part of the thing that we're doing.
Specifically talking about the armory rotation.
In that agreement, the city was responsible for the law.
The argument is all we can tell you.
All we can tell you is including natural deaths and everything that we're going to tell you.
In this note, very much.
The proposal agreement that they're looking at.
They're going to maintain a lot of their own equipment.
The equipment, your arm, the institution.
Because they built them.
When they read in that building, everything there starts to grow.
They equipment.
Everything comes to them.
So they're going to maintain their own equipment.
And they're going to take on the, the old supernatural deaths.
So that is a huge help in public works.
Because, just for example, we have that gas door.
So it's probably a long time.
So that would be $12, $1,000, $13,000, $12.
So just the way that goes.
And just the history of the Israelis all around a double.
$20, $20, $20, $20, $20...
They make it subtle.
We have got it that it takes hours, we can move it, I mean.
They're going to make it and get it in some things.
So that's huge help to us.
One of the big things about this proposed agreement is the MSRP program.
This is something that I can go back and look in the notes.
It was talking back and back in 2012, accounts were talking about it.
The same thing like this, read this, that every couple of years, and just can't count to the three of us.
But I think we probably can't say I have you meeting him on this.
RHSRP program is strictly a suburb program that promotes health and active.
It's outdoor gym activities.
You know, that's not the fact.
There's really no staying or staying program.
And it is only a month of June, and RHSRP 714.
This is an opportunity to run a gym and the engine body with a larger record
and way more activities than what we did off.
Talking about the cost for MSRP program.
From 2014 to 2023, we averaged about 39,000 for that program over those years.
But that's for one month.
And that's all we've got to run that program.
We have seen the participation drop in the last half of the years.
Why?
Why are they already in one of the boys and girls above?
Or they cannot count us.
And as we only offer from nine to one, we'll offer that to them.
We don't know.
But we've seen the major decline in RHSRP and MSRP.
So as far as it goes on the public work side, it's dead.
It's dead in the work of scoring this agreement because it's something we've been trying
to propose in my account for years.
I think it's going back to the 12th of a month or the minutes, and I'm just asking for you back.
Now this is a paper for how the dollar gets red thing.
So it's not a budgetary thing.
It's very important.
It's on your utility bill assessment, and we would just be shifting some of that
and some of that kind of thing.
Do the boys in girls club, for dinner, and stay in their summer program.
And that's how people go on.
But they're paying in a lot more.
5.
Margin, I would like boys in girls club.
Questions?
When you say stuff, some of those moms and people said the money you spend,
the insurance will be broken, $50,000.
Is that what you expect?
He transferred to the police department.
Yeah.
The dollar didn't exactly go full in for a day and a summer program.
It generates a costly, and then only $60,000.
So $50,000, and that will go to the boys and girls club,
to write a summer program.
First summer program is worth this all of.
Another thing I want to disagree with, and I want to touch on just briefly,
is Chris, who came up with a suggestion that, rather than waging all utilities,
that they need to regret it.
And we often present it, and you want to see that in that program.
So now, they have skimmed again on their retail.
Right?
The city, the city, the city, the city, the entire bail,
the entire pay, the percentage, other retailers.
So the utilities are moving from our name to the earnings.
So the way we're responsible for paying that bail,
just like you know, outside organization, we help,
and then we'll issue that program.
Quite frankly, that methodology is something moving to school.
It's never a bad idea for someone who's responsible for turning off
and off that lives and being conservative.
If they've got skimmed again, we have to do this too.
It's a better use of city funds than other people.
It's plenty of charity and not just her or shift to everyone.
And everything in this area has nothing to do with it.
The boys and girls club have access to it, swimming pool,
for years at no charge, now it's in the streets.
They want to use the jag as now, so when we help you to break that out of our costs for the year, you know, why it's that you can see that, is it different?
They've said the list today that Scott Holmes will take you home and he says, are you all those things hiring to back in New York?
We're still in New York, I think.
Thank you.
I'll do this.
I mean, if we can read this in the post of Mr. Github.
We can't stop for this.
I love America.
We can get you done for this.
Well, say you made it to me, ladies.
I don't know.
The team, this team without big teams, we'll be back for it.
We can be in the classroom for purposes of executive session.